Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 1 (donated 1990), 1976-1990; Series 1; 82 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1976-1990; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Upshur Street Clinic, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Upward Mobility College, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Urban Corps Expansion Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Urban Development Action Grant, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Urban Food Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Urban Land Institute, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Urban Service System Corp., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Urban Village,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - V Street N.W.,1300 Block - Pest Control, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Valley Vista Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Vanata Grads,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Sons of Varik, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Vendors (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Vendors (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Vendors (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Venture Concepts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Vermont Ave. Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - 1812 Vernon Street,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - 1825 Vernon Street - Tenants, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Verona Apt., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Vickerman and Schultz,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Victims Assistance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Victory Awards, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Vigil Against Violence (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Vigil Against Violence (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - E.F. Vines and Associates,M.B.A, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Union University, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - The Vision Foundation,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Visiting Instruction Service, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Visiting Nurse Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Visitors' Services Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - Vista International Hotel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Voluntary Organization in Concern for the Elderly (VOICE), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - Volunteer Clearing House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - Voter Registration Drive, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Voting Record of Chairman Clarke-1990, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Voting Record of Chairman Clarke-1989 (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Voting Record of Chairman Clarke-1989 (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Voting Rights Amendments, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - 1430 W Street,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - W Street Task Force, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - WAMU, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - WAMU-FM Station, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - WDCU-FM Jazz 90, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - WDJY-FM, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - WJLA, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - WKYS-93.9 FM, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - WMAL AM, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - WPFW, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - WRC-TV Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - WWAS Honors Dinner, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Waiver of Compensation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Wakefield Hall Apartments, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Walk Against Fear, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Walk for Hope, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - H.L. Walker and Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Walker and Dunlop,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Walker-Jones Elementary School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Walker Memorial Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Ward Coordinators Meeting, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Ward One (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Ward One (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Ward One (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - Ward One (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - Ward One (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Ward One (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Ward One Community, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Ward One Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Ward One Council on Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Ward One Council On Human and Community Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Ward One Democrats (1 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Ward One Democrats (2 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Ward One Democrats (3 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Ward One Democrats (4 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Ward One Democrats (5 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Ward One,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Ward One Planning Community Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Ward One Schools, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Ward One Tenants Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Ward One Tenants Political Action Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Ward Two Democrats, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Ward Two Tenants Council (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Ward Two Tenants Council (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Ward Three Democratic Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Ward Four Democrats, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Ward Five City Council Candidate, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Ward Five Council On Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Ward Five Democrats, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Ward Five Festival / Arboretum Youth Group, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Ward Five Residents on Upsher - 20th Street, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Ward Six Democrats, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Ward Seven Citizens for Progress, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Ward Seven Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Ward Seven Community Retreat, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Ward Seven Merchants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Ward Eight, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Ward Eight Democrats, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Warner Theatre, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Warwick Condominium, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Dianne Warwick Day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Washington Adventist Hospital, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Washington Afro-American, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Washington Airport Task Force, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Washington Area Bankers Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Washington Area Bicyclist Association (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Washington Area Bicyclist Association (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Washington Area Bicyclist Association (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Washington Area Coalition Against Registration and the Draft, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Washington Area Consortium on HIV Infection in Youth, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - Washington Area Council on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Washington Area Council on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - Washington Area Federation for Progress, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - Washington Area Lawyers for the Arts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Washington Area Music Association,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 30)
    - Washington Area Training Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 31)
    - Washington Association of Black Journalists (WABJ), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 32)
    - Washington Bar Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Washington's Bid to Host World Soccer Cup Games in 1994, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Washington Board of Realtors,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Washington Building and Construction Trades Council,AFL-CIO, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Washington Business Journal, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Washington "Bypass"--Outer Beltway, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Washington Cathedral and Mount Saint Alban, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - The Washington Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Washington Center for Aging Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Washington Center for Learning Alternatives, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Washington Chamber Political Action Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Washington Child Development Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Washington Churches for Social Action,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Washington Coalition of Churches, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Washington Committee for Good Government, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Washington Communications,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Washington Convention Center (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Washington Convention Center (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Washington Correctional Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Washington Council of Agencies, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Washington Court, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Washington Design Center (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Washington Design Center (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - Washington,D.C. Coalition of Neighborhood Business and Professional Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Washington,D.C. International Urban Fair and Parade, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Washington,D.C. Ophthalmological Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Washington,D.C. Parent Child Center (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Washington,D.C. Parent Child Center (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Washington,D.C. Parent Child Center (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Washington,D.C. Parent Child Center (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Washington,D.C. Retail Liquor Dealers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Washington Development Group, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Washington Dossier, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Washington Dulles Task Force (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Washington Dulles Task Force (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Washington Free Clinic, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Washington Gas (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Washington Gas (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Washington Gas (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Washington Hairdressers and Cosmetologists Association of the District of Columbia, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Washington Half Way Home For Women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Washington Harbor Association (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Washington Harbor Association (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Washington Healthcare Corp., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Washington Hebrew Congregation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Washington Highland Community School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Washington Highlands Branch Library, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Washington Hilton (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Washington Hilton (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Washington Home, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Washington Home For The Blind, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Washington Hospital Center (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Washington Hospital Center (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Washington Hospital Center (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Washington House Apartments, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Washington Humane Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Washington Independent Bus Guild,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - The Washington Informer Newspaper, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Washington Inner city Self Help (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Washington Inner city Self Help (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Washington Inner city Self Help (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Washington International School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Washington International Trade Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Washington International Youth Hostel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Washington Is A Capital City, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Washington Jewish Week, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Washington Kidney Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Washington Living Magazine, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Jobs Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (1 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (2 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (3 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (4 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (5 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (6 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (7 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (8 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (9 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (10 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (11 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (12 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (13 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (14 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (15 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (16 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (17 of 17), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Bus (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (1 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (2 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (3 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (4 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (5 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (6 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority- Metro Rail (7 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Washington Museum of Contemporary Art, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Washington National Cathedral, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Washington Orphan Asylum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Washington Parent Group Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Washington Peace Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Washington Post, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Washington Post Magazine Recall Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Washington Pretrial Justice Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Washington Primary Care Network, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Washington Project for the Arts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Washington Psychiatric Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Washington Real Estate Brokers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Washington Redskins, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Washington Sangerbund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Washington Saturday College, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Washington Senators Fan Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Washington Society of Association Executives, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Washington Teachers Union (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Washington Teachers Union (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Washington Theatre Laboratory, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Washington Times, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - Washington Treatment Center (1 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - Washington Treatment Center (2 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - Washington Treatment Center (3 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    - Washington Treatment Center (4 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Washington Treatment Center (5 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Washington/Tucker Tribute, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Washington Urban League (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Washington Urban League (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Washington Urban League (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Washington Urban League (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Washington and Vicinity Federation of Women's Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Washington Women's Arts Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Washington Youth Gardens, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Washingtonian, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Washingtonview, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Watchword, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Watergate East, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Waterside Towers Residents Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Watson Funeral Home, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - The Way of the Cross Church of Christ,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Weatherization Programs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Webster House Tenant Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 158, Folder 19)